<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Luis Wenus</title>
    <link>https://luiswenus.github.io/luiswenus.com/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Luis Wenus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://luiswenus.github.io/luiswenus.com/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Worldcoin</title>
      <link>https://luiswenus.github.io/luiswenus.com/projects/worldcoin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiswenus.github.io/luiswenus.com/projects/worldcoin/</guid>
      <description>Coming soon&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Airbnb for Storage</title>
      <link>https://luiswenus.github.io/luiswenus.com/projects/stowe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiswenus.github.io/luiswenus.com/projects/stowe/</guid>
      <description>After finishing my Africa trip, I had to go to university. With US universities being too expensive, the UK seemed like a good compromise. I ended up getting an offer from Imperial College London to study Mechanical Engineering, after flying from Barcelona to London to conduct my interview, already on my way driving to South Africa. I was thinking much more about the Africa trip than Mechanical Engineering at that time, so I&amp;rsquo;m glad I got in, and somehow even got a scholarship covering my tuition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Driving From Munich to Cape Town</title>
      <link>https://luiswenus.github.io/luiswenus.com/projects/tourdeafrica/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiswenus.github.io/luiswenus.com/projects/tourdeafrica/</guid>
      <description>Why? Growing up, I always loved adventures. Anything from visiting old castles to climbing the fence of old military camps around Norway. I decided once I got my driving licence: the ultimate freedom, I had to do some sort of crazy trip.
My criteria for this trip was:
It had to cost less than $5k It had to be to countries no one goes to so I&amp;rsquo;d have cool stories Covering a large distance Ideally starting my drive from home I started reading on what trips &amp;ldquo;overlanders&amp;rdquo; (people who travel in 4x4 cars) were doing at the moment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The website with 1M hits: ratemyteacher.no</title>
      <link>https://luiswenus.github.io/luiswenus.com/projects/ratemyteacher/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiswenus.github.io/luiswenus.com/projects/ratemyteacher/</guid>
      <description>The problem I went to a state-school growing up, which meant mediocre education and unfirable teachers. I had my trouble with some teachers through the years, often because I either knew more than them or they were just inadequate at their job. I also had some incredible teachers who had such an impact on my life that I to this day have a deep interest in subjects they taught. The sentiment around these teachers went by word of mouth through students, but there was no channel for students to give this feedback directly to teachers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 14 Year Old Web-Designer</title>
      <link>https://luiswenus.github.io/luiswenus.com/projects/dinenettsider/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiswenus.github.io/luiswenus.com/projects/dinenettsider/</guid>
      <description>I grew up in a family of four kids, which already was an expensive endeavour by my parents. We also had family abroad and most extra money was spent on travel there. The mantra was always: you want money to spend, you need to earn it yourself. I was 14, and needed to make some money.
The idea I had already manifested from an early age that I wasn&amp;rsquo;t going to work for anyone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Random stuff I&#39;ve built</title>
      <link>https://luiswenus.github.io/luiswenus.com/projects/randomstuffibuilt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiswenus.github.io/luiswenus.com/projects/randomstuffibuilt/</guid>
      <description>This page is just to manifest some of the things I was building growing up.
The Snowmachine I always loved snow, and hated the part of the winter before the snow fell. We usually have around a month of this in Norway, and I desperately wanted to get snow in my garden before everyone else. Snowmachines obvously exsisted, but were way out of my price range, so I had to build my own.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
